>> Kyle Simpson: 未定义与未声明的快速注释。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: A quick note
on undefined versus undeclared.
这通常是混淆的。
This is often confused.
这很困惑因为开发者很自然地
And it's confused because developers,
quite naturally,
将这些词视为同义词。
think of these words as sort of synonyms.
他们好像是差不多一样的意思
They seem like they mean kind
of almost the same thing.
用英语来说那可能是真的
And in English, that's probably true.
但在编程中，这完全不是真的。
But in programming,
it's entirely not true.
在编程中，尤其是在 JavaScript中，
In programming, and
especially in JavaScript,
这是两个完全不同的概念。
these are two entirely different concepts.
所以在前一张幻灯片上，当我说 V 型的时候，我收回了报价，
So on the previous slide, when I said
type of V, and I got back quote,
未定义的 V 或任何变量都是不存在的。
undefined, V or whatever that variable is,
didn't even exist.
我怎么能在什么都不知道的时候再引用
So how is it that I can get back quote
undefined when something doesn't even
是否存在?
exist?
那是另一个历史上的疣 JavaScript 试图假装
Well, that's another historical wart,
JavaScript trying to pretend as if
没有宣言就没什么大不了的
the absence of a declaration
isn't that big a deal.
这不是一个大问题，你可以在它周围工作。
It's not that big of a problem,
you can work around it.
事后看来，他们绝对不应该这样做。
In retrospect,
they never should have done that.
它们应该已返回未声明的字符串。
They should have just
returned a string undeclared.
未声明的表示它从未在我们有权访问的任何范围内创建。
Undeclared means it's never been created
in any scope that we have access to.
没有定义的意思是肯定有一个变量在那一刻
And undefined means there's definitely
a variable, and at the moment,
它没有值。
it has no value.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 非常不同的事情。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Very different things.
>> Kyle Simpson: 运算符的类型是唯一存在的运算符
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: The type of operator
is the only operator in existence
它可以引用不存在的东西而不抛出错误。
that is able to reference a thing that
doesn't exist and not throw an error.
>> Kyle Simpson: 现在，未定义和
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Now, undefined and
没有声明我们可以直截了当地筛选出来
undeclared, we can fairly
straightforwardly sift those out.
但在引入的语言中还有一个空虚的概念，
But there's another concept of emptiness
in the language that was introduced with,
本质上是 ES6
essentially, ES6.
而描述这一问题的最佳方式是未初始化。
And the best way to describe
this is uninitialized.
另一个提及这一问题的方法
Another way of referring
to this particular
变量可以被称为 TDZ，即时间死区。
condition that a variable can be in is
called the TDZ, the temporal dead zone.
我们会在接下来的讨论中得到更多的信息
We're gonna get much more into this in
our next unit of discussion when we talk
关于作用域的信息。
about scopes.
我们要谈谈这东西是从哪里来的
We're gonna talk about where
this thing comes from.
但基本上，这个想法是某些变量，比如块作用域，
But essentially, the idea is that certain
variables, like block scope ones,
别被初始化
don't get initialized.
它们最初从未被设置为未定义。
They never initially get set to undefined.
当某些内容处于未初始化状态时，它将处于关闭状态。
When something is in an uninitialized
state, it is off-limits.
不允许您以任何方式，形状或表单来触摸它，也不允许您发生错误，并且
You're not allowed to touch it in any way,
shape or form, or you'll get an error, and
您获取的错误是 TDZ 错误。
the error you get is the TDZ error.
这也是我们这个空虚的另一个概念。
So it's yet another concept
that we have of this emptiness.
我们可以有一个从未被初始化过的变量。
We can have a variable that's
never been initialized.
我们可以有一个未定义的变量已初始化。
We can have a variable that's been
initialized that is undefined.
或者我们可以有一个从未被创造过的变量，然后它就被取消了。
Or we can have a variable that was never
even created, and then it's undeclared.
我们需要用三个不同的概念来总结我们的大脑。
Three different concepts that we
need to wrap our brains around.